d3ayat.com 2016-11-06

# d3ayat Online Business Directory - Privacy Statement

**d3ayat Privacy Statement**

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site [www.d3ayat.com](http://www.d3ayat.com/). Here we disclose the information gathering and dissemination practices for our site.

When we collect personally identifiable information about our customers, we at d3ayat comprehend the importance of protecting their privacy. We owe this privacy policy to our website visitors, subscribers, users of our services, buyers of our products, and our advertising customers.

**Protecting personally identifiable information:**

While providing our services, we may collect your information for obvious reasons. We also ensure that we inform you the reason behind the collection of private information. Sometimes, the service providers or agents do this job for us. Other public documents and other company databases may become our source for collecting private information about you.

**How we use your information?**

The personal information like your name, address, telephone number, and/or financial details in some cases may be necessary for us to collect. While online, you click on certain pages within our network and we collect information regarding that. We abide by the rule that sensitive information is not collected. At times, if we do require some crucial information, we will seek your consent before collecting such information. Your information is required to fulfill certain administrative operations like billing, marketing, customer relationships, and also during third party contracts. When you post an advertisement with us, we can use the personal information contained in that used by us for publication in other media, as per the terms and conditions of that publication.

We may share your personal information with some other companies in Saudi Arabia that are related to d3ayat. Those companies or we may utilize your personal information for improving our products and services.

**Third Party Use-**

We may share your information to d3ayat’s service providers and contractors in order to provide and market our products to you. The third parties who provide reader offers or prizes may also know your information. At the same time, we take care that the third parties also take extreme care about your personal information as we do.

**Log Files:**

We also collect certain non-personal information like identity of your Internet browser, type of operating system you use, your IP address, and the domain name of your ISP. This is required to optimize our services. We may utilize this non-personal information for improving content of our site. We at d3ayat may use personally identifiable information to accentuate our services and improve our goods including web sites in aggregate form. This information may help our website respond competitively to the needs of the customers. The analyzed information or statistical data may be used as a report for marketing, advertising or research purposes.

**How to work towards your Security-**

The security, integrity, and privacy of our customers are of utmost importance to us. Different physical and electronic security tools are used at d3ayat and restriction of physical access to our offices and firewalls is maintained. This saves your information from misuse, loss or unauthorized use.

_However, no data transfer over Internet can be guaranteed as totally secure._ ** ** _The information you post in chat-rooms or bulletin boards is public information and d3ayat cannot guarantee the security of this public information._

**Access to personal information-**

You reserve the right to have access to the most personal information we have collected about you. You also have the right to know if this access is denied. You can contact our Privacy Officer for gaining access to your information.

**About Cookies-**

The data transferred by website to individuals hard drive for record keeping are called cookies. Cookies can aid in accentuating the users access to site. Cookies help track usage patterns and also help us formulate data to improve our content and target advertising. With the simple procedure in your browser, you can accept or deny the “cookie” feature. But for features like merchandising transactions or registered services, cookies are necessary.

**Online third-party links-**

We may allow our visitors to establish links with the sites operated by our partners. These sites may be co-branded with our logo but we may not operate these sites. These sites also may collect personal information from you and share with us. This privacy policy also applies to such collection of personal information.

However, d3ayat is not responsible for the contents of these third party websites. However these links do not constitute endorsement, approval or sponsorship of practices of third party sites.

**Be careful about your privacy on internet-**

After you are done with your user session, close your browser. By doing this, you prevent others from accessing your personal information especially if you share your computer with someone else or if you are using a public computer. You are responsible for your own computer security. Your disclosure of personal information on the Internet can be collected and used by others. Especially if you post personal information in online forums, you may receive unsolicited messages in return. You are responsible for the secrecy of your username and password, so be careful while on the Internet!

Kindly contact our [Privacy Officer for Access](mailto:webmaster@d3ayat.com) to your information. You can also lodge a complaint about the information policy here and also can get more information regarding privacy concerns.

**Write to:  ** **d3ayat Webmaster** ** **[ **webmaster@d3ayat.com**](mailto:webmaster@d3ayat.com)
